前集剧情摘要
以后你可能不能跟我联络
You may not be able to contact me.
-为什么? -我得搞定查裴尔
- Why? - Chappelle became a problem.
所以他们怀疑到我了
I had to take him out of play and they're onto me.
-他们很快会带我走
- They'll take me out soon.
-我要跟谁求援?
- Who do I contact if I need help?
蜜雪儿会用远程存取 尽力来协助你
Michelle is setting up an offsite station.
-你被捕了， 蜜雪儿在哪里? -我知道她在哪里
- You're under arrest. Where's Dessler? - I can find her.
抓到了， 她已被逮捕
Affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
琴?哈罗
Kim? Hello?
-你是谁? -我是凯蒂华纳
- Who are you? - I'm Kate Warner.
你父亲要我来接你
Your father sent me to come get you.
我爸怎么会叫一个 他刚认识的人来接我?
Why would my dad send someone he'd just met to come get me?
他信任我
He trusts me.
我们越早离开
The sooner we leave, the sooner
你就越早能跟你父亲相聚
you and your dad can be together.
司法部长说你要找我
The Attorney General said you'd want me for your counsel.
-他们怎么说的?
- What have they told you?
-你被卸职了
- You've been removed from office.
这个证据 被彼得金斯利所利用
The evidence was manipulated by a man named Peter Kingsley.
我要你尽全力调查这个人
I need you to find out all you can about him.
-怎么帮你?
- What happens now?
-只剩最后一招， 交出金斯利
- We got one last play. Deliver Kingsley.
他这人极端危险 而且你没办法接近他
He's far too dangerous, and you'll never get close to him.
说的对， 是你不是我去
You're right. I won't, but you will.
金斯利不知道修特已死
Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's dead.
就说你要交出修特
If you say you can deliver him,
就会引起他的兴趣
that should get his attention.
我要我们谈话的录音带
I want the tapes that you made of our conversation.
我会用修特做交换
I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
洛城体育馆 18号出入口， 30分钟
All right. LA Coliseum, gate 18, 30 minutes.
-反恐小组有什么支援? -什么都没有
- What support will you get from CTU? - As of now, none. Ow!
Jack? Jack!
以下是发生在早上 7点至8点的事
还好吗?
- You OK? - Yeah.
快呀
Come on.
车子发不动 我们下车
Dammit. The car won't start. We gotta get out of here.
安全带卡住了
My seat belt's jammed.
派默夫人， 请你帮我
Mrs Palmer, I'm gonna need your help.
请不要这样
Mrs Palmer, please don't do this.
抱歉， 我得顾我自己
I'm sorry, but I have to take care of myself.
等我可以了我会叫救护车
When I'm free I'll call an ambulance.
-不可以这样 -别无选择
- You can't do this! - I don't have a choice.
你很棒， 可惜你对善恶太分明
You're a very impressive man, but you see everything
就像大卫一样
as either good or bad, just like David.
-这世界是很复杂的 -是很简单的
- The world is so much more complicated. - No, it's simple.
一场战争快要开始了
There's a war about to start and you're
你是唯一可以帮我阻止此事的人
the only person who can help me stop it.
-不为总统吗? -他离弃了我
- What about the president? - He turned away from me.
25年的生活， 建立的家庭
After 25 years of building a life together,
他却离弃了我
a family, he turned me away.
他们最后还是会知道是你的
Eventually they will connect you to this conspiracy.
核弹本来是不该引爆的
That bomb was never supposed to go off.
事情本来不该是这样的
None of this was supposed to happen this way.
我知道， 我相信你 但你可以阻止此事的
I know. I believe you. You can put an end to it now.
帮我捉到金斯利
If you help me get Kingsley,
你丈夫会重新出任总统
your husband will get his presidency back.
那会是你的功劳
That will be because of you.
派默夫人， 求求你
Mrs Palmer, please.
Goddamnit!
你要我怎么做?
What do you want me to do?
置物箱里面有小刀 帮我割开
There's a knife in the glove box. Help cut me out.
进来吧
Come on in.
这样好多了， 比较简单
This is much better. It's simpler.
我们必须想办法说明
We gotta be able to explain this thing.
-麦克， 我有事跟你说
- I need to talk to you, Mike.
-我五分钟后下来
- I'll be down in five minutes.
麦克
Mike.
很重要
It's important.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
什么事?
What is it?
这是金斯利的档案
It's a file on Peter Kingsley.
几分钟前调出来的
They pulled it up a few minutes ago.
杰克鲍尔 认为一切都是他主使的
Peter Kingsley, the man Jack Bauer thinks is behind the bomb.
他在约六小时前打电话
There's a record of phone calls he made,
给一名叫做乔纳森华的军人
as recently as six hours ago, to a soldier named Jonathan Wallace.
那军人就是 珊瑚蛇突袭队的人
Wallace was a member of the Coral Snake brigade.
明显的是他杀了自己人
He apparently killed his own men.
我知道他是谁
I know who Wallace is.
轰炸机刚通过最后的哨站
The planes have passed over their final checkpoint
一小时内就会到达目的地
and will reach their targets within the hour.
主攻击目标是军事单位
Our primary targets are all military,
但那是个位于住宅区域
but one includes a command-and-control
的指挥中心
center inside a residential area.
不论我们武器有多精确
As smart as our weapons have become,
都会产生间接伤害
there may be some collateral damage.
会伤到平民
You mean civilian casualties.
Yes, sir.
-无可避免吗? -没办法
- There's no way to avoid these? - I'm afraid not.
那我们就只好这么办
Then it's something we're just gonna have to live with.
我是查裴尔
Ryan Chappelle.
-我是麦克纳维 -有什么事， 长官?
- Ryan, this is Mike Novick. - How can I help you, sir?
我知道有人对有关塞浦路斯
I know there's been some confusion today
录音的真假有所争议
about the veracity of the Cyprus audio.
不是的，我们的鉴定
Not really. Our teams came
与兰利那边的是一样的
to the same conclusion as Langley.
那鲍尔还在寻找
Do you know if Bauer's still trying to find
伪造录音的证据吗?
evidence that the recording was fabricated?
对， 他未经授权
Yes, but he's operating outside our authority.
我要你协助他的调查
I want you to assist his investigation.
-长官， 我根本不知道他在哪里 -那就找到他
- Sir, I don't even know where he is. - Then find him.
为何要我这么做?
I'm not sure why you're asking me to do this.
我们不是该准备作战吗?
I was told we're at war and to proceed accordingly.
还没有
We're not at war yet.
30分钟内给我
You have 30 minutes to report back to me
杰克所找到的结果
the findings of Bauer and your efforts.
-可是长官... -这是命令
- But sir... - That's a direct order, Ryan.
你知道我的联络方式 用这条专线回报给我
You have my channel. Call me back on this line. That's all.
-我要过一小时才上飞机 -为何要延迟?
- I'll be on the plane in an hour. - Why the delay?
核弹引爆地点不对
The bomb detonating in the wrong location
所以有些额外的工作
created a little extra work.
不必担心什么， 我希望
Nothing to worry about, I hope.
不会的 我不想烦你了
Not at all. I won't bore you with the details.
你讲
Bore me.
我还得处理修特
I still have to take care of Alex Hewitt.
修特是唯一的证人了
Hewitt is the only one who can bring this whole thing down.
-你不是说已经处理掉他了
- You told me you'd have him by now.
-我找不到他
- I wasn't able to find him.
我会处理的 别担心
But I'm taking care of it. Don't worry.
你们俩， 坐下
Sit down, both of you.
你不必对付蜜雪儿
You don't need Michelle here.
她只是听命行事
She was acting under my orders.
-我自己来讲 -我要你们坐下
- I can defend myself, Tony. - I said sit down.
我要你们帮我 联络杰克鲍尔
I need you to get me in contact with Jack Bauer.
我明白了， 杰克上面有人支持
Oh, I see. Jack got some support above you
现在你有压力了
and now you're being squeezed, right?
-到底办不办得到?
Can you do it or not?
-是怎么一回事?
What's goin' on?
或许杰克找到的证据是真的
Bauer's evidence might actually have some relevance.
-所以我们是对的
- Which means we were right.
-不， 你们差点害死我
- No. You damn near put me in a coma.
竟敢攻击我
That's assault.
我告诉你 你不要对付我们
I'll tell you what. You drop the charges against us...
我们就会帮你
and we'll help you.
少来了， 雷恩 所有人都会建议你这么做的
Come on, Ryan. You of all people know that's your best move.
-好吧 -白纸黑字
- Fine. - In writing.
好的， 写下来 快帮我找到鲍尔
All right, in writing. Just get me in touch with Bauer.
-不找人支援吗?
- Shouldn't we call for help?
-我现在不是听命于反恐小组
- I'm not working under CTU's authority.
-对他们来说我并不存在 -所以我们只能靠自己
- To them I don't exist. - So we're out on our own.
完全靠自己
Completely.
-你还好吗?需要帮助吗? -他受伤了
- Are you all right? You need some help? - He got hurt.
-可以送我们到医院去吗? -好的， 当然
- Can you get us to a hospital? - Uh, yeah, sure.
-派默夫人， 你来开车 -什么意思?
- Mrs Palmer, you need to drive. - What do you mean?
-抱歉， 我们要用你的车
- Sorry, but we need your car.
-别紧张， 拿去， 开走吧
- Hey, easy, all right? Go ahead, take it.
谢谢
Thank you.
已经好了， 长官
They're ready, sir.
-我姓华纳， 嗨， 卡丽你好 -嗨， 凯蒂
- Miss Warner. Hi. Carrie Turner. - Hi. Kate.
-你一定就是杰克的女儿 -我爸在哪里?
- You must be Jack's daughter Kim. - Where's my dad?
他还在外面， 等一下
He's still in the field. Wait here.
我去告诉查裴尔你们来了
I'll tell Ryan Chappelle you're here.
-让我来处理 -你不是被看管了
- I'll handle this. - I thought you were in custody.
已经释放了
I was released.
琴， 我知道出了什么事 你还好吧?
Kim, I heard what happened to you. Are you all right?
应该没事， 我想看我爸爸
Yeah, I guess so. Look, I just wanna see
我要知道他是否有事
my dad and make sure he's OK.
他现在不在
No, he's not here right now.
要几个小时才会回来
He won't be back for a couple of hours.
-他知道我在这儿吗?
- Does he know I'm here?
-他若来电我们会告诉他
- No. We'll tell him when he phones in.
-杰克说我们一到达就要打给他
- Jack insisted we call as soon as we get here.
-现在电话接不通
- He's just not reachable now.
卡丽会带你们到后面休息
I'll have Carrie take you back and
我马上就过来
get you situated. I'll be there in a minute.
不会有事的
It's gonna be OK.
OK.
华纳小姐?
Miss Warner?
不知你是否知道
I don't know if you're aware of this but...
你父亲被释放后有回来
your father came back here after we released him.
为什么?
Why?
他要在你妹妹被带走前 和她讲几句话
He wanted to talk to your sister before she was taken away.
玛莉被带到这边吗?
- They brought Marie back here? - Yeah.
你欺骗了我?
You lied to me?
你杀了理沙?
You killed Reza?
还想杀你姐姐?
You tried to kill your own sister?
你真的想引爆核弹
You were willing to set off a nuclear bomb
害死上千万人?
in a city with ten million people?
告诉我为什么? 因为我必须了解
You tell me why. Because I need to understand.
告诉我你是被逼的
Tell me that they forced you to do it, that they
你被洗脑了，你受到威胁
brainwashed you, that they threatened you.
告诉我你不知道 自己在做什么
You can tell me that you didn't know what you were doin'.
一定是有理由的
There must be a reason.
没有理由， 爸爸
There is no reason, Dad.
我不能接受
I can't accept that.
我也不能
I couldn't either.
当时她举起枪对着我要扣扳机
Until I looked into her eyes and she pointed
我看着她的眼睛
a gun at me and started to pull the trigger.
相信我， 爸爸
Trust me, Dad.
她不会回答你的
She's not gonna give you any answers.
她无法做到 那是我们无法理解的原因
She can't. At least, nothing that we could ever understand.
爸...
Dad...
好了 我们走
Come on. Let's go.
凯蒂
Kate.
你以为在外面会安全
You think you'll be safe out there.
其实不然
You won't be.
-我是东尼 -你复职了吗?
- Jack, it's Tony. - Tony, you back in play?
琴已经到这里了
Yeah. Jack, Kim's here at CTU.
-她很安全 -谢谢老天， 别告诉她我的事
- She's safe. - Thank God. Don't tell her what's going on.
-就说我很快会回来 -我会的
- Just say I'll be back as soon as I can. - I will.
-我是雷恩， 我们得谈谈 -你这浑蛋
- Jack, this is Ryan. We need to talk. - You son of a bitch.
是你阻止救援的直升机
You stopped that chopper picking up me and Hewitt.
-害修特死掉， 这要你负责
- Hewitt's dead. I hold you responsible.
-现在不一样了
- Listen, things have changed.
你有完全的支持 告诉我现在的任务
You got full support. Give me your mission profile.
我要去见金斯利
I've set up a meeting with Kingsley.
在洛城体育馆18号出入口
We're gonna meet him at the LA Coliseum, gate 18.
派默夫人会让他确认
Mrs Palmer will wear a wire and make him confirm
事情与那三个国家无关
that the three countries had nothing to do with the nuke.
想办法撑到后援到达
Stand down until you get some support.
很快就会到了
Our people will be there soon.
没时间了
We don't have time.
现在就要和金斯利会面了
Kingsley's expecting the meet to go down now.
你需要后援
You need backup.
你想帮忙， 就找出金斯利
If you wanna help me, get me voice prints of
与派默夫人的声纹做确认
Kingsley and Mrs Palmer for authentication.
好了
Done.
-还要与白宫现场语音传输
- And a live audio feed to the White House.
-需要通到总统吗?
- You want an audience with the president.
Yes.
好吧， 线路不要断掉
All right. Keep the line clear.
-收到， 我们要进体育馆了
- Copy. We're pulling into the Coliseum now.
-赶快派迅雷小组到那里去
- We need to get a SWAT team to his location.
停在那里
Pull over there.
在这里等我
Wait here for me.
过来
Come on.
我帮你装窃听器
Let's get you wired.
脱掉外套
Take yourjacket off your shoulder.
这是无线发讯器
This is a wireless transmitter.
不会被他们知道
They won't know to look for it.
也不会被发现
They won't be able to trace it.
-这太疯狂了， 不能单独行动
- This is crazy. We shouldn't do this alone.
-别无选择
- We don't have another choice.
金斯利没有见到
Remember, Kingsley doesn't want
修特不会走的
to leave here without Hewitt.
这就是我们的优势
That's gotta be to our advantage.
讲话
OK, say something.
我好怕
I'm scared.
可以用
OK, it's working.
总统先生
- Yes, Mike. - Mr President,
我现在推翻自己
I am against any delay in our military actions.
从一开始反对延迟开打的立场
I have been from the start.
因为现在很有机会取得
But there is a good chance we'll receive
伪造塞浦路斯录音的证据
evidence soon the Cyprus recording is false.
我们都知道第二波带了核弹入境
We know Second Wave brought the nuke into the country
也知道这一切
and we know they're sponsored by
都是那三个国家赞助的
these three countries. What am I missing?
虽然现在还没有细节
I don't have all the details,
但我刚发现一个线索
but I just learned about a possible link
第二波与一个 叫金斯利的男子有关联
between Second Wave and a man named Peter Kingsley.
他是谁?
Who is he?
他控制里海油田
He's apparently part of a consortium of oil interests
with contracts in the Caspian Sea.
是油田的人主使核弹的吗?
An oil consortium's behind the nuke?
鲍尔相信他能让金斯利讲出实话
Bauer believes he can get a confession
他要现场语音连线
from Kingsley. He's set up a live audio feed.
轰炸机再20分钟就要轰炸了
Our bombers are due to drop their payloads
in less than 20 minutes.
鲍尔马上要和他会面了
Bauer's meeting Kingsley any minute.
这是现场语音声纹传送
This is the live voice print.
这是纪录上的对照语音档
And this is the voice file we have on record
这可以证明说话的人 的确是雪莉派默
which will prove that it is, in fact, Sherry Palmer.
-确认了 -下面这个是金斯利?
- It's confirmed. - The one below is Kingsley?
-你们收得到吗?
- Yeah. - Are you guys getting this?
-很清楚 -多久后援会到?
- We're good here. - How far out is our backup?
-11分钟
- They're 11 minutes out.
-太久了， 现在就要进去了
- That's too long. We've gotta go now.
-等一下 -不行
- Just wait. - We can't.
我们已经迟到10分钟
We're already ten minutes past
普雷斯科特准备好了吗?
the meeting time. Is Prescott ready?
东尼已经接上白宫
Tony's on with the White House.
正在设定现场语音传送
They're setting up a live audio feed.
好， 那一切就搞定了
OK, good. We are set to go.
你那边如何?派默夫人?
How are you doing, Mrs Palmer?
万一金斯利要杀我呢?
What's to prevent Kingsley from shooting me?
没看到修特之前 他不会动手的
He won't do anything until he gets Hewitt.
但是一旦他发现 修特不在我们手上...
But the moment he realizes we don't have Hewitt...
我会掩护你的
I'll be covering your back.
你这种状况 让我不能安心
That's not very comforting considering the condition you're in.
我可能不会活着走出来
I may not make it out of this.
我不想骗你 那是有可能的
I'm not gonna lie to you, Mrs Palmer. That's a possibility.
我这么做是为了大卫 你很清楚， 对不对?
I'm doing this for David. You know that, don't you?
对
Yes.
你会告诉他吗? 万一出了什么事情
Will you tell him that? In case something happens.
我会的， 派默夫人 你过去吧
I'll take care of it, Mrs Palmer. You've gotta go now.
-麦克 -是的， 长官
- Mike. - Yes, sir.
传输连线已经准备好了
We just finished setting up the feed.
希望这不是浪费时间
I hope this isn't gonna be a waste of our time.
相信我， 总统先生 我也一样
Believe me, Mr President, so do I.
怎么了， 麦克?
What's going on, Mike?
总统与我都觉得这件事 应该也让你参与
The president and I thought you should be part of this.
普雷斯科特与司法部长
Along with Prescott and the Attorney General,
都会一起听现场语音传送
we will be listening to a live feed.
-听什么? -对付彼得金斯利的秘密行动
- Of what? - A sting operation against Peter Kingsley.
他主使核弹之事
It appears he was the architect of today's bombing
并以塞浦路斯录音栽赃
and the delivery of the Cyprus audio.
鲍尔找到金斯利
- Bauer found Kingsley. - Yes.
但是要与金斯利对话的 不是鲍尔
But it won't be Bauer who'll be talking to Kingsley.
只要能让他认罪
What difference does it make
也没什么差别
as long as we get him to incriminate himself?
有什么事?麦克
What is it, Mike?
是雪莉要与金斯利对谈
It's Sherry who'll be talking to Kingsley.
我不懂
I don't understand.
看来几个月前 金斯利找了她串通
It seems that Kingsley recruited her some months ago.
她也参与其中
She was part of this.
雪莉为金斯利工作?
Sherry was working with this man, Kingsley?
看似如此， 长官
It appears that way, sir.
引爆核弹并挑起战争? 不会的
To detonate a nuclear bomb and start a war?
No.
目前不清楚她了解多少 或牵涉有多深
It's unclear how much she knew, or how deep she was in it.
希望她能引出金斯利认罪
We just have to hope she can extract a confession from Kingsley.
现在雪莉与鲍尔配合
So now Sherry is working with Jack Bauer
要把金斯利引出来吗?
to bring down Kingsley?
她要冒相当的危险
Yes. And at considerable risk to herself.
史考特 我没有指示前别动作
Scott, don't do anything until I tell you to.
-我们需要修特 -了解
- We need Hewitt. - Understood.
-修特在哪里? -他很安全
- Where's Hewitt? - He's safe.
他在哪里?
Where is he?
你骗我， 你根本 就计划要引爆核弹
You lied to me. You wanted this bomb to go off all along.
你利用了我与罗杰斯坦顿
You used Roger Stanton and you used me.
是的， 没错
Yes, I did.
现在我被你牵连
Well, now I'm tied to you, and
也与核弹牵连，我要求自保
the nuclear detonation. I want safe haven.
-那是你的问题 -现在是你的了
- That's your problem. - Well, I just made it yours.
我若出事 你也别想见到修特
Because you won't see Hewitt until I'm safe.
-你别想骗我 -你也别当我是呆子
- Don't horse trade with me. - Don't insult my intelligence.
-找到符合金斯利的声音 -雷恩， 听到没
- We got a match on Kingsley's voice. - Ryan, you got it.
不交出修特你就别想走
You're not going anywhere till I have Hewitt.
这不是让你来决定的
That doesn't work for me.
等我离开到安全之处
I'll call you on this line to give you
我才会打电话告诉你他在哪里
Hewitt's location after I'm safely away.
我不会让你知道我的行踪
You don't need to know where I'm going.
-没有我们要听的
- We're not getting what we need here.
-她会问出来的
- She'll get it for you.
-录音带的问题要解决
- Now there's the matter of the recordings.
-都在这里
- They're right here.
我们之间所有的通话录音
Every phone conversation between you and me.
不， 我要全部 包括塞浦路斯的
No. I want all of them, including Cyprus.
为什么?那与你无关
Why Cyprus? You had nothing to do with that.
要保障
- lnsurance. - lnsurance?
只要一开战
Once the country goes to war, the
政府也不会发表此证据的
government will never let that be exposed.
修特是唯一能伤害我们的人
Hewitt is the only one who can hurt us.
-因为录音是他伪造的 -对
- Because he forged the Cyprus recording. - Right.
-证据都有了， 我们走
- You got your proof. Let me go ahead.
-让白宫先确认
- Get it confirmed from the White House.
-她必须赶快抽身 -满意了吗?
- She can't stay much longer. - Are you satisfied?
反恐小组要知道 这样的证据是否充分
CTU wants to know if that's enough to prove it.
有确认过这声音真的是现场
Have you confirmed this is live
并通过鉴定?
and the voices have been authenticated?
是的， 长官
Yes, sir.
那就够了
- So that's it. - Yes.
等我降落， 我再打电话给你
When I land... I'll call you.
你在唬我 修特根本就不在你手上
You're bluffin'. You don't have Hewitt, do you?
-是真的 -不， 是假的
- Oh, yes, I do. - No, you don't.
史考特， 杀了她
Scott, take her out.
干掉她
Kill her.
雪莉， 快跑
Run, Sherry!
快点
Come on. Come on.
雪莉， 快离开， 快
Mrs Palmer, get out of here. Go!
杰克鲍尔
Jack Bauer.
你今天给我很多麻烦了
You've caused me a lot of trouble today, Jack.
你不会交出修特， 对不对?
You're not gonna give me Hewitt, are you?
轰炸机离目标只有三分钟
Our bombers are three minutes from the targets.
开始探戈一号第六一程序
lnitiating sequence six one tango one.
目标出现， 武器锁定
Target in view. Weapons lock.
要开始攻击吗?
Are we go for a strike?
可以发射了吗?
Are we go for a launch?
我们已经待命中
We are awaiting command.
取消攻击
Abort the attack.
取消， 取消
Abort, abort.
什么意思?金斯利死了? 怎么会这样?
What do you mean, Kingsley's dead? How could that happen?
我警告过你不要用他
I warned you not to use him.
我们用了他， 但失败了
So we did use him and he failed.
没关系 只要战争一开始就好了
But it won't matter. Once the war starts we'll be OK.
-不会开始了 -为什么?
- It isn't going to start. - Why's that?
总统已经知道录音的事
The president found out about the Cyprus
取消攻击了
recording and called off the attack.
不会开战了， 麦克斯
There isn't going to be any war, Max.
我们得用另一种方法来
Well, we're going to have to do this another way.
-另一种方法，你在讲什么?
- Another way? What are you talking about?
-你会知道的
- You'll find out.
今天就会开始
It'll start today.
是我， 开始吧
It's me. Go ahead.
内阁取消之前的决议
The cabinet has annulled its earlier action.
我已经请特勤组
I have instructed the Secret Service
恢复对您的服务
to resume its charge of serving you
您现在是美国总统
as President of the United States.
我明白了
I see.
我也已经提出辞呈 即刻生效
I've also tendered my resignation, effective immediately,
所有投票反对您的内阁
and those members of the cabinet who voted
也已经都同意辞职
against you have also agreed to resign.
吉姆
Jim.
各位先生， 女士...
Gentlemen, ladies...
今天我们几乎 要发动无谓的战争
we came dangerously close to war today.
大家对核弹爆炸之事
That all of us reacted emotionally
感到情绪化是可以理解的
to the nuclear detonation is understandable.
但身为领袖
But leaders are required
必须比常人更具耐心
to have patience beyond human limits.
我们所要采取的行动
The kind of action we nearly took should only be exercised
应该在所有证据查明后方可执行
after all other avenues have been exhausted.
必须透过最严苛的求证
After the strictest standard of proof has been met.
你们草率的隔离我
By casting me aside so quickly,
只会降低求证的水准
you effectively lowered those standards.
这是很大的错误
And that was a profound mistake.
但是我相信 以后绝不会再发生这种错误
It was not, however, a mistake you're likely to make again.
所以我不接受你们的辞呈
Therefore I do not accept your resignations.
我们今天要赶快安定国家
We have a nation to heal today.
你们每一位都担负着 重要的任务
And all of you play a vital role in that healing process.
总统先生...
Mr President...
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
不必说了
There's nothing to say.
还有很多工作要做
We have work to do.
就这样子
That'll be all.
-珍妮， 准备开记者会 -几时?
- Jenny, set up a press conference. - When?
尽快 我要公开一切
As soon as you can. And I want it public.
我要直接面对人民
I want to speak to the people directly.
他们需要我给的保障
They deserve my assurance.
是的， 长官
Yes, sir.
麦克， 我要谢谢你
Mike, I wanna thank you again
在最后关头找反恐小组的人
for calling CTU in the 11th hour.
不客气， 总统先生
Of course, Mr President.
你本应该 与我共同坚持到底
But you should have been with me to the end.
这是我对你的期望
That's what I expected of you.
所以我才对你交付重任
That's why I appointed you.
现在你可以卸职了 即刻生效
I'm relieving you of your post, effective immediately.
好的， 总统先生
Yes, Mr President.
谢谢你， 长官 我不能占功劳
Thank you, sir. I can't take all the credit myself.
乔治・梅森所带领的人员 都很出色
It's a great team George Mason put together here.
我知道 谢谢， 长官
Yes, I will. Thank you, sir.
是总局局长范恩
Tony. That was District Director Vaughn.
他对今天我们的表现大感高兴
He's so happy with what we did here today
不知要从哪里开始讲
he doesn't know where to start.
太棒了
That's great.
怎么了， 朋友?
So what's up, my friend?
是...
Well...
是这样的
it's like this.
你若不开除我
Either fire me...
就请马上离开我的位置
or get out of my chair.
这位置是你的
The chair's all yours.
轮班的人到了 他们都得到交接资料了
The new shift is here. They've been brought up to speed.
我想去接我哥回家
I was thinking I'd get my brother and go home.
今天的少数人
Michelle... there's a handful of
创造了很大的成绩
people who made a big difference today.
你也是其中之一
You're one of 'em.
你下了难以抉择的决定
You made some tough choices and
而且反抗过我，但你是对的
went up against me. You were right.
谢谢
Thanks.
赶快回去休息吧
So why don't you go home and get some rest?
Michelle.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
-我得检查袋子里的东西
- I'll need to see the contents of your bag.
-我是凯蒂华纳，这是琴鲍尔
- I'm Kate Warner and this is Kim Bauer.
借过
Excuse me.
-嗨， 亲爱的 -爸爸
- Hey, honey. - Daddy.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be all right.
我知道
I know.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
爸， 我要照顾你
Dad? I'm gonna take care of you.
我要强烈的要求你们
I urge you in the strongest terms
不可对现在或可能会听到的
not to indulge any rumors or theories
不实传闻与谣言加以渲染
that you may have heard, or may soon hear.
一旦全部事实查明后 我会亲自对各位发布
Once the facts are known, I will present them to you myself.
在此之前， 大家都要知道自己很安全
Until then, know that we are all safe
也不会再有任何危险
and that we will continue to be safe.
今天大家可以充分表现出的
The most patriotic thing that we can all do
爱国精神就是好好的过日子
today is to keep living our lives.
我呼唤大家， 回到工作岗位 回到学校去
So I urge you all, go back to work, go back to school.
因为我们所享受的自由
Because the freedom we enjoy,
每天所得到的自由
the freedom that we earn every day,
就是我们用以战胜敌人的一切
is the very thing that will defeat
也是让我们坚强的理由
our enemies and keep us strong.
天佑美国
God bless America.
天佑吾民， 谢谢
God bless us all. Thank you.
非常谢谢 主保佑大家
Thank you very much. God bless you.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢， 见到你们真好
Thank you. Good to see you.
谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
总统先生
Mr President!
嗨
Hi.
抱歉， 总统先生
Excuse me, Mr President.
谢谢
Thank you.
总统先生
Mr President.
-嗨 -谢谢
- Hi. - Thank you.
-主保佑你 -谢谢
- God bless you. - Thank you.
-喂 -完成了
- Yes. - It's done.
谢谢
Thank you.
总统先生?
Mr President?
总统倒下了 快找医护人员， 救命
The president's down! We need medical assistance. Help!
快搜查那个人
Search that man right there!
-总统先生? -检查武器
- Mr President? - Check him for weapons!
总统先生? 不会有事的
Mr President? It'll be all right, sir.
需要救护车， 快点
We need an ambulance! Help!
Merge Subtitles: Sunpiny